Is this your plan?
To be the next Mr. Aragon.
I thought you were the head of PR.
I wasn't aware
that you're an aspiring gigolo
and a gold digger on the side.
If I do want to go back to school,
I will be the one deciding.
Not because it's what she wants.
And most especially not
because I owe her anything.
-The partnership will pull through?
-Yes.
We don't have problems anymore
because everything has been cleared
and they value our competence
more than the rumors.
So get to work.
Make sure everything is prepared.
I have nothing
to be ashamed of. I fought back.
The victim should not
suffer embarrassment!
Who should be embarrassed are the creator
and the person
who showed it to the public.
I will never let myself
be a mere victim in your eyes!
I thought all the footage had been erased.
Ricardo said he got rid of all the copies.
He has all the copies?
Then he leaked the video!
Why would he do that?
Why are you defending him?
You know what happened to Patricia,
but you kept it from me!
Why didn't you tell Martin about this?
What are you trying to prove?
That you're a hero?
Martin is still Patricia's father.
It was Patricia who decided
not to tell you.
Whether she likes it or not,
I have the right to know
because I'm her father!
-I'm protecting my daughter!
-You let her get humiliated!
Why is this my fault?
You can't protect our daughter.
I'm not surprised.
You've always been like that ever since.
Martin.
That's the flash drive I brought in, sir.
Then, where did that video come from?
I swear, sir, I have nothing
to do with that video.
I want to check the CCTV footage.
We don't know how this happened, sir,
but the CCTV camera
in the control area isn't working.
Let me see.
-Clara.
-Yes, sir?
Where are the people from Burger City?
The transition team
went back to their area,
but Mr. Smith went home already.
Where's Ms. D, by the way?
-I'll go check on her.
-Okay, sir. Excuse me.
You!
We're really sorry, Martin.
We'll find out what happened.
You bastard!
You're the only one
who has a copy of that video!
Are you accusing me?
Tell me.
Where were you
when your daughter was in trouble?
Shouldn't you be protecting her?
You're useless!
Hey!
-Come on! Fight!
-Martin!
-Calm down.
Let's fight!
Is that all you can do?
Fight with your fists?
-I'm sorry.
-That's enough.
I don't fight weak people.
-Martin!
-Martin, I said that's enough!
Sir, there's a commotion
at the events room.
What?
Ricardo, Martin, stop it!
-Sir!
-That's enough!
-Enough.
-Sir, please. Stop fighting.
-Stay out of this!
-Stop it!
-Martin! Martin!
-Sir, that's enough.
-Dad! Dad!
-Martin!
-Dad!
-Patricia.
-I'm sorry, Patricia.
-Come on.
I didn't want to fight back,
-but your father kept provoking me.
-You bastard!
Patricia, please take your father outside.
This is all your fault, Diana.
Her life's been a mess since she got here!
Don't you see?
The people who want to destroy you
are also going after her!
Dad, that's enough.
Let's go home. Come on.
-That's enough.
-Let's go.
Watch your step.
Let me check your hand.
Dad, why did you do that?
Why are you blaming your father?
He was the one who got hurt.
You're the one I should ask, Patricia.
Why didn't you tell me
that happened to you?
Why?
I don't want to add to your problems.
I don't want to be a burden.
What, you think we can't protect you?
You probably think…
-I'm weak.
-No, Dad.
Tell us, Patricia.
Are we a burden to you?
I mean, we'll be fine. I have a job now.
I will not abandon you.
You're not a burden to me.
I'm doing all of this
because I love you all so much.
Dear…
I don't want you to lie to me.
Don't keep secrets from me ever again.
Promise me that.
Yes, I promise.
I'm sorry.
You acted like kids.
Who did this?
We're still investigating.
But whoever did it
has access to the control booth,
so that means they're part of La Familia.
So, it's because of my enemy again?
This is an attack against me.
It's because of me.
They should've just attacked me instead.
Why…
Why would they drag my daughter into this?
They should've just left
my daughter alone.
Not my daughter. No.
They should direct their anger at me.
It should be me, not her.
I'm the one they should attack.
Not my daughter. No.
-Sir, good evening.
-Hmm?
I'm Carlo Lozano.
I'd like to file a report…
about La Familia.
Ms. D, Sir Ricardo…
Have you found out what happened?
The original AVP
on the control booth's computer
was switched to Patricia's video.
There's also a technical problem
with the CCTV cameras,
so there's no footage.
That's… That's impossible.
How did the security breach occur?
Why don't we investigate
from where it all started?
You're the only one who has the video.
How come someone else got it?
And why did they target
the sole heiress of La Familia?
Teddy, what are you trying to imply?
The truth!
Mrs. Aragon.
What now?
Help!
It's you! This is the guy who attacked me!
-How dare you!
-Ma'am!
-Damn you!
-Ma'am Diana, believe me.
-I didn't want that to happen.
-Yes, right!
I have no choice.
I was paid to do it.
But my conscience is eating me away.
Who told you to do it?
Tell me!
It's him.
Your brother.
It was your brother who gave me orders.
He ordered me to attack you.
Liar! I don't know
what you're talking about!
I have proof.
Sir Teddy and I spoke
on the phone several times.
He gives me instructions on what to do.
He told me to decline
the settlement offer,
prolong the negotiation process,
and stage a rally outside your office.
-That's not true!
-But…
when Ma'am Patricia talked
to some of our group members,
they agreed to accept La Familia's offer.
I couldn't convince them anymore,
so he started to threaten me.
He said I have to follow his orders
and attack Ma'am Diana.
-Take that back!
-Teddy, relax.
Don't touch me!
-Relax.
-You were the one who gave him orders!
-What are you talking about?
-You have his phone!
You even threatened me!
Diana, don't believe him. It's all a lie.
He's out of his mind.
Please, please, please.
-Why?
-No, no.
-No.
-Why?
I'm your sister.
-Yes.
-I'm your sister.
We checked Carlo's phone,
and we have confirmed his statement.
-Give me that!
-Teddy!
-Give me that! Give it to me!
-Sir! Sir! Wait!
-Wait! Let go of me!
-Relax, sir.
I said let go of me!
-Let go of me!
-Come on!
Ms. D.
We found some footage
of what happened earlier.
We didn't get anything from the CCTV,
but the cameramen
were testing the cameras before the event.
They got a video of what was happening
at the control booth.
It was Georgia who did it?
That's not true! That's not true!
It's fabricated! It's fake!
-It's fake!
-Shut up! Shut up, Teddy!
Enough!
Okay. Thanks, Enzo.
What did he say?
It was Uncle Teddy and Georgia
who released the video.
Wait. How did they get the video?
They don't know.
The police are taking them
to the police station.
Those bastards!
-Come on, let's go.
-No need, Dad.
Let's leave it to them.
They can handle it.
That family is really something.
They spare no one.
For what? For money?
And they dragged you into all this?
And what did your mother do?
She didn't do anything, did she?
You were the one who defended yourself.
Mom, that's enough.
Maybe you should quit your job
at La Familia.
Hold on, Martin.
Why would you want Patricia
to quit her job?
She has to prove herself
to them more than ever.
You're the only one
who has the right to inherit all that.
They can all leave, but not you.
-What are you doing?
-Hey!
I can file charges for that.
Diana asked me to come here.
I don't need you!
Bribery, obstruction of justice,
serious physical injury, attempted murder.
Those are some of the charges
that can be filed against you…
based on Carlo's testimony and evidence.
Do you think you can intimidate me?
Just to remind you,
I'm an Aragon.
Teddy.
Your being an Aragon is useless
if Diana decides to abandon you.
Do you think you can
get away from all this, huh?
Tell me.
What's your problem, huh?
Why are you doing this?
I'm not doing anything.
I can see right through you.
It takes one to know one?
Our lawyers are on their way.
You won't be able
to prove the accusations.
You know, I could help you.
We should be helping each other.
But you did this to yourself.
Hmm…
Dad… Dad… Dad…
Dad, I don't want to go to jail.
I don't want to go to jail, Daddy!
You see…
ever since we were kids,
Teddy felt like I was Dad's favorite.
When he was younger,
he was always left alone.
That's why he's constantly
seeking attention.
He grew up…
always needing to prove something.
That he deserved more?
Dad gave me all the responsibility.
He told me I was the eldest.
So I should act like one…
and take care of my brother.
I can't abandon him.
I never meant…
for us to compete.
I think…
he doesn't want to just compete with you.
He wants to beat you.
So he doesn't care who gets hurt
as long as he wins.
He even wants…
to destroy Patricia.
Maybe I'm just forcing…
what I want on Patricia.
But now she's getting dragged
into this mess.
Maybe I really don't know…
how to be a good mother.
If only Patricia knew…
I'm trying…
I'm trying to be a good mother.
But…
I wasn't raised to be soft.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Why did you bring me here anyway?
We are here to… let it all out.
If you're angry… if you want to curse…
if you want to scream,
let it out.
-No.
-Curse them all out. Like this.
You animals!
You bastards!
-Uh…
-Try it.
I don't think so.
Come on, Diana. You can do it. Try it.
You shameless bastards!
Diana, you can do better than that.
Come on. Scream.
Let it out!
Curse them out.
You shameless bastards!
You animals!
You demons!
Damn all of you!
I'm not a bad person.
I'm a good person.
I did everything for my family.
I did everything for them.
It's okay.
This is just how I was raised.
This is how my father raised me.
I'm not a bad person.
It's okay. It's okay.
Thank you, Attorney.
But this isn't over yet, Teddy.
They'll still investigate you thoroughly.
I'm ready.
Just make sure
my daughter doesn't get charged.
Georgia's case will be easy to resolve.
They won't find any evidence against her.
You have nothing to worry about.
Okay?
-We'll be in touch.
-Okay.
Sir.
Ms. D wants to speak with you.
Sis.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
Why did you do that?
How could you do that to me?
Everything Carlo said was a lie.
They're not true. He's lying.
-Oh, come on.
-I could never hurt you.
I could never hurt you.
Why would I even do that?
And someone gave me that USB.
They said it was urgent
and needed for the program.
So, I just gave it to them.
Please, Sis…
Please believe me.
I admit I wasn't careful.
I let someone who wanted
to hurt you use me.
-It's my fault, but I--
-Oh, come on!
Come on, Teddy! Don't take me for a fool!
You're so shameless!
-You're an ingrate!
-Sis, please…
-How could you do that, Teddy?
-Sis, please believe me…
Please believe me!
-Get up!
-Please, Sis!
-I said get--
-I'm begging you! Please…
-Teddy, get up!
-Please believe me!
I could never do that to you!
Sis, I could never do that to you…
Please. I didn't do it!
Please believe me…
Diana…
-Sis… Sis…
-How could you…
How could you do that to me?
-My goodness, Teddy!
-Sis…
Please…
I'm your big sister.
Come on.
Do you remember that I was the one
who took care of you when you were little?
I was the one Dad would scold
whenever you did something wrong!
Dad always reminded me
I should be responsible
because I'm your big sister.
I'm sorry. Sis… Sis… Sis, please…
Whenever you'd cause trouble,
I was blamed and punished, too!
You bastard!
Sis… Sis…
Dad always told me…
we're a family. And family…
should always look out
for each other no matter what!
But to what limit?
You also hurt my family, Teddy!
Patricia's my daughter, remember?
She's also your family, you bastard!
I'm sorry, Sis.
You bastard.
How dare you!
-You're so shameless!
-Sis…
Sis…
Patricia.
Wow.
Chin up.
Don't worry about me, sir.
I can handle it.
It's okay if you can't.
Thank you.
You've got this.
-Oh, there's Patricia.
-Let's go.
-Patricia.
-Patricia, are you okay?
Don't think about it anymore.
We believe you, friend.
I hope they catch whoever did that to you.
You're a good person.
They shouldn't have done that to you.
-Mm-hmm.
-Keep fighting.
You got this, girl!
-You've got this.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, everyone.
-We're here for you.
-Let's go.
Are you okay?
You should be recycled.
Plastic.
Enzo told me what happened last night.
Did he also tell you
there's no evidence against me?
That's why I'm here.
You're so shameless.
It was an honest mistake!
How was I supposed to know
that USB had your filthy video?
But you know what? You are the mistake.
I hope Aunt Diana never let you in here.
Because no matter how much
you pretend to be talented,
you will never amount to anything.
You have nothing to show for yourself.
Patricia, what are you doing?
-Let go--
-Between the two of us,
you're the useless one.
If you were so talented,
you wouldn't have to humiliate me
-just to secure your position here!
-Let go of me, Patricia!
Come on!
Don't push me, Georgia.
I fight back.
Don't test my patience.
Remember…
Between the two of us,
I am more worthy.
-Okay?
-Let go of me.
Argh!
What are you doing?
Where are you taking this?
Give it to me! Give it!
What's this?
Sir Teddy, you're being transferred.
Ms. D's orders.
What? She's demoting me?
-Lateral transfer.
-What position?
I can't be removed as CMO.
You're being transferred
to Marketing and Distribution
as Executive Director.
If you have any questions,
you have a scheduled meeting with HR.
They will introduce your new team,
discuss your scopes,
-and--
-You can't do this!
You can't do this, okay?
I'll talk to her myself.
I've even apologized to her.
Why did you apologize to her?
I'm the one you and your daughter hurt.
You didn't expect that I'd fight back.
I'm no pushover.
Patricia, look…
I'm sorry.
Okay? I'm sorry.
Patricia.
Ms. D needs to speak with you.
My arm still hurts because of that woman.
That bitch Patricia.
You should've seen her earlier.
Oh, she's really violent.
Are you okay?
Obviously not.
What did you say?
What did Patricia do to you?
I'll go now.
Nothing.
Nothing?
I heard you. So, what did Patricia do?
Patricia blames me for the video,
but I really had nothing
to do with it. Okay?
I just don't like how he treats my dad
in this company.
Hey. Ouch! Excuse me?
You just need some ointment.
Here.
If you ever need anything,
don't hesitate to come to me.
But aren't you Patricia's mom?
Stepmom.
Diana is her mother. Take this.
Just give that back to me later.
Evil stepmom…
You called for me?
How are you?
I don't really have a choice
but to be okay.
What's this?
Your full payment.
That's the remaining balance
of 800,000 pesos.
Why?
You want to silence me
about what happened?
To cover up for Uncle Teddy?
Is that what you think?
Isn't it?
I thought that's what you wanted.
Full payment.
You're just giving it to me
just like that?
Patricia, I am giving you a chance
to take control of your own life.
So you can decide what to do next.
Because I don't ever want you
to think I'm holding you back.
You're playing the good guy again.
It's so easy for you
to give up on me, isn't it?
Well…
you never defended me, anyway.
A lot of people are waiting
for my downfall.
And they'd drag you down with me.
I'm protecting you.
Are you leaving?
What do you think?
Should I make my life easy?
Should I leave all of this?
That would be a waste.
You're good, Patricia.
And you matter here.
I mean…
You are an asset to this company.
And no matter what happened,
I know you can bounce back.
Plus, you're growing close
to the people here.
A lot of people believe in you, Patricia.
For the first time,
you and Ms. D see differently, huh?
Who told you that
we see things differently?
What does that check mean?
I've seen this before in TV shows.
She just wants you
to make decisions for yourself.
Well, isn't that what you want?
She wants to protect her eldest child.
Huh? Eldest?
You don't have siblings, right?
La Familia!
La Familia comes first.
Only La Familia matters.
Because of me,
the great reputation
of La Familia is ruined.
That's why she wants me gone.
I am the dead weight.
I am the disgrace.
I am worthless.
That's not true, Patricia.
That's not true.
If you leave,
it's like telling those who dislike you
that you've lost.
That your name really has been ruined.
Don't give them the satisfaction
of thinking you gave up.
Instead,
prove to them
why you deserve to be here at La Familia.
Are you okay, Patricia?
Mm, I'm clocking out.
Patricia.
Sir.
-Going home?
-Yes, sir.
I heard you talked to Diana.
News travels fast here in La Familia, huh.
-Have you made a decision?
-I'll think about it first.
If you ask me, don't leave just yet.
But if you think it's time
for you to leave,
no one should stop you.
Follow your dreams.
In the short time we've had here,
you've only ever succeeded
by following your heart.
-All right, I'll go ahead.
-Take care.
It's no joke how many times
you made us come back
-just to get our money.
-Give me a break.
What matters is that you're getting paid.
-What if we asked for interest?
-There's no need for that.
Please count it. That's complete.
-We're all paid up.
-Go on now, you can leave.
-Thank you very much.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, Patricia.
Dear, where did you get the money?
Ms. D gave the full payment.
Does that mean
you can leave La Familia now?
What if Patricia leaves for good?
Back to how it was.
Whatever I do,
she still thinks badly of me.
-Has anything changed?
-Yes.
Even if you don't tell me, I can feel it.
Before, you only protected La Familia.
Now, you protect Patricia too.
You're blaming yourself.
You've never given up on La Familia.
I wish you were like that
with Patricia too.
I didn't give up on Patricia.
How can I protect her
if she doesn't trust me?
Sometimes the heart acts before the mind.
Diana…
don't let your relationship
be ruined, okay?
You should fight together.
So, have you made your decision?
I've paid off my father's debt in full.
Good.
Your father won't be
a problem for you anymore.
You can do what you want for yourself now.
You're right.
So, I've made my decision.
I'm not leaving.
-Will that get filled?
-Yes.
-Expecting a big win?
-You know how it is…
-Remember our deal, okay?
-Hey, guys.
-Hey, man!
-Martin!
-You're starting early today.
-Want to place a bet?
What's that?
Ending.
Sure. Hold on.
-That's what I'm talking about!
-Here's 200 pesos.
0-9 and 0-1.
-All right then.
-Nice.
Come join us for a bit.
-Come here.
-Yes, sit right here with us.
Sure. Hold on a second.
Here.
-I'll just log this in.
-Go ahead.
Have a shot first.
Well, it's still early.
-That's it.
-There you go.
Why? Do you have somewhere to be?
Why? Do you guys have jobs?
There aren't any gigs.
My wife has a job,
she earns her own money.
My kid just got paid.
Well… you guys are still strong.
You drink pretty hard.
I raised and supported my kids.
Naturally, it's their turn to support me.
We should really benefit
from our children.
It doesn't work that way.
Come on, we're the same, Martin!
The only difference is your daughter
will be a millionaire.
You're just waiting to hit it big, right?
-Drink up for the jackpot.
-Yes, jackpot.
Guys, I'm not relying on my daughter.
I'm just looking for an opportunity
to bounce back.
I'm going to start my own business.
Sure, whatever you say.
-Come on, let's drink.
-Let's drink to that!
-Drink up.
-Hold on.
-My kids are here.
-Wait, finish this first.
-Hey, just this one!
-Next time, next time.
-Thanks, appreciate it.
-I know, right?
-Drink all of it.
-Bless me, Dad.
-Go on inside.
-That's fine.
-Mm-hmm.
-Here you go.
-Are you tired? You okay?
-Another shot.
It's tiring, Dad.
If nobody wins here…
-It's ours.
-Of course!
-We'll take it all.
-Shot, shot!
As per your instructions,
I talked to the lawyers about Teddy.
I also told the witnesses
not to release these yet.
I'm having them gather their statements,
so at least we have something.
But essentially,
it's a closed case for now.
Okay.
Yes?
Diana, are you sure?
What do you expect me to do, Ricardo?
Power grab? Scheming?
It won't help the company
if that comes out.
Teddy is my brother.
But they'll still think
you're favoring him.
I manage what I can control.
Teddy is one of them.
Now, if our suspicions about him are true,
he can't bring me down anyway.
He's not that competent,
and his influence in the company
isn't that broad.
And what makes you think
I won't hold him accountable?
I'll make sure he learns his lesson.
You're not deciding
as the CEO of La Familia.
You're deciding as a sister.
That's what Dad taught us.
Never to wash our dirty linen in public.
Because those who want to bring us down
will use that as ammo against us.
Why? Do you have
a lot of dirty laundry hidden?
We're done here.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Sir.
I'm fine.
Looks like you want
to kick someone in real life.
Who? Teddy?
Well, Diana doesn't want the news to leak.
That's why she won't press charges.
Yes, I get that.
When did she not put La Familia first?
Nothing matters more
than the company's reputation.
What is my humiliation worth to her?
Patricia, Diana is just doing
what she thinks is right.
For herself.
For your family.
Maybe she thinks when she retires,
she'll have no one else
to rely on but Teddy.
Teddy will continue La Familia.
You have no interest in La Familia, right?
I was surprised you lasted.
I didn't stay for her.
I'm here
to prove to all of them that I can do it.
It's hard to prove yourself…
to someone who doesn't trust you.
But I trust you.
I know you can do it.
So don't worry,
just because Teddy got away
with what he did to you…
doesn't mean he won't pay.
What do you mean?
Patricia, people like Teddy…
won't stop
until they get what they want.
They won't stop pulling foolish tricks.
But don't worry.
If he does something stupid,
I'll be there to stop him.
And I'll make sure
even his name won't be able
to save him anymore.
Why are you doing this?
Because we're on the same side.
I can see myself in you.
I started from the bottom as well.
I worked my way up without anyone's help.
I know how hard it is.
If I can do something so people
won't go through the same thing,
why not extend the help I can?
There's no need for that.
I won't be affected
by what Uncle Teddy has to say.
Because I know that between us…
I'm definitely kinder than he is.
Ms. D, I already moved your 3 p.m. later.
Just move everything to tomorrow.
-Okay, will do.
-Okay.
-Ms. D.
-Where is Patricia?
The marketing department gave her a task.
Uh, tell her to go to my office
right after, okay?
I think…
she's trying to avoid you, Ms. D.
Because?
With all due respect,
we can't really blame Patricia
for feeling bad about what happened.
It wasn't easy for her.
She got humiliated in front of everyone.
Is that what you think too?
That I chose Teddy?
It's an easy assumption to make, Ms. D.
There's nothing easy
about the decisions I make, Enzo.
There are lots of things to consider.
I always need
to look at the bigger picture
because there's so much at stake.
It doesn't mean
I'm not doing anything about it.
She knows you did that for the company
and for the family.
But Patricia is also your family, Ms. D.
What are you trying to say, Enzo?
I hope you don't get me wrong.
I am not questioning your decisions.
But Patricia doesn't see
the bigger picture
you're talking about, Ms. D.
She sees this whole situation
as your daughter.
And she thinks…
you made a choice
and it wasn't her.
-Oh!
-Oh! Sorry.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
Sorry.
Good morning, ma'am. How can I help you?
-I want to inquire about enrolling.
-Here.
Why are you pacing back and forth?
Mom and Sis aren't replying to me.
Maybe Sis is just busy at work.
Jena.
What's this about
that you need to bother
your mom and your sister?
What do you want? Tell me.
Uh, Dad…
I need money.
But it's for our school's fundraising.
We organized a beauty pageant.
How much do you need?
-Three thousand pesos.
-What?
Son of-- That's huge!
Will that get you higher grades?
Dad, please!
Fine. Just don't bother them.
If I win at gambling later,
I'll give you the money.
Remember my classmate, Michelle?
She said she'll pay for the venue.
She'll rig the contest and win for sure.
I hate it!
Rich people always
get everything in their favor.
Don't worry, dear,
we'll recover from this.
It's okay, Dad.
I've accepted our situation.
You don't believe me?
Uh, I've got things to do.
One… six.
All right. Put it inside.
Do you really think we're done?
I know you're behind everything
that happened to me.
All the lies they pointed at me
were your doing.
You know, Teddy, I think you need a break.
I know it's hot out.
The heat may have gotten into your brain.
No.
I know that was you.
The person who attacked my sister
and the food poisoning
in the feeding program,
that was all you.
Careful now. You don't have any proof.
That might cause you more harm.
You really don't know me well.
I don't know which ring of hell
you came from,
but don't worry, I'll find out.
You're the one who should be careful.
Help Teddy.
He can't do all the heavy lifting.
Have you found a side gig yet, bestie?
I called the producer earlier.
They said there's one.
Oh? What role?
Maybe you can bring me along.
Well, that's the thing, bestie.
I tried asking the producer,
but they don't want to hire you anymore.
It seems like you've been
blacklisted or something.
And the director's been badmouthing you.
Wait, I'm the victim here.
I know, bestie.
But you know how things work here.
If they have it out for you
and you're not famous,
there's nothing you can do.
But why are you looking
for another gig anyway?
I thought you were doing okay
with La Familia.
I can't just rely on that.
Besides…
I want to go back to school.
Well…
Can you really juggle all of that?
Oh, that's easy!
It's not like you don't know me!
I'm a hard worker, see!
Oh, wow, you really are.
A hard worker at eating buns.
-I'm right, aren't I?
-Wow!
Benjie, can't we leave yet?
We have a flat tire, Ms. D.
Again?
There's a nail in the tire.
-What?
-Right here.
Diana.
Did you get a flat tire?
Do you think you can fix it?
Yes, Ms. D. Uh…
But I need to take the car
to a tire repair shop.
It might take a while.
You know what, I'll give you a ride.
You look tired, too.
By the time Benjie finishes there,
you'll be tired and hungry.
And there's traffic, too. Come on.
Yes, Ms. D. After this,
I'll bring the car straight home.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
You know, I have a reservation.
Do you want to come with me?
Or you know what, better yet,
let's just go to your place.
It's quiet there.
I've been missing home-cooked food.
Excuse me.
You're getting a little too casual
with me now.
Is that a bad thing?
Just don't get used to it.
We're strictly co-workers.
Yes, ma'am.
Nanny, please prepare dinner for two.
Good evening.
Is it good?
Sorry? Oh! The sushi?
Yes, it's pretty good.
That's good.
Nanny?
Nanny!
Don't you have something to do?
How about your duties?
Oh, right. I do have something to do.
-Call me whenever you need me.
-Yes! Yes.
Are you close?
Yes.
She's been taking care of me
since I was a child.
She's also been like a mother to me.
So she's been with you
for a long time, huh?
Mh-mm.
Next time I come back here,
I'll bring her a gift.
Next time?
She's such a great cook.
I ate so much.
Is it okay if I always eat here?
Maybe when I come back,
there will be a sign posted there saying,
"Ricardo Banned.
Reason: He eats too much."
"Ricardo, you're such a PG."
Do you know what PG means?
Professional Glutton.
Ricardo.
It's getting late.
Go home after you eat.
Okay.
Cala Soda is mine!
I'm telling the truth!
You're all thieves!
All the evidence against Patricia
has been deleted.
So everything can be pinned
on Cecilia Pineda.
Make sure nothing about this gets out.
I'm already gaining her trust.
I'll avenge you.
Ms. D wants you
to help her plan the new campaign.
I'm just adding to her list
of disappointments.
-Stop worrying!
-Do you have a thing with Enzo?
-Where did that come from?
-Enzo and I used to be a thing.
We've been separated for years.
Haven't you moved on?
Do you really think
your relationship affects me?
Someone sent me a message threatening me!
-I'll protect you.
-Don't you think you trust him too much?
I want to know who's doing this to me.
Whoever did this is going to pay.
I'll destroy them.